hello everyone
this is richard with hydrogen technology
today.com
once again final view of the 2003
f-150 with the triton 5-4 liter motor
this is my hydrogen assist fuel cell
installed
uh you know what i've basically done
here is dremeled out a little bit of the
plastic
that cell fits real snug in there it's a
very nice fit
it rests the bottom of it rests right on
a ledge if you can see that ledge
and it rides very nicely i've got my
positive lead
my negative lead the negative comes
directly
from the battery you can get a peek at
that
the positive comes directly from my dash
mounted
or it's sitting on my dash i should say
on off switch and we'll follow that wire
on over into that
pardon the bad camera work open my door
up here
give you a peek at what happens when i
flip the switch
there's my module basically it it only
comes on when the truck is running so
that's the
hydrogen on demand part of all this
go ahead and turn my key you can get a
look out my window while i do this
okay key is on and
notice the the unit is not on which
means i'm not producing hydrogen i'll go
ahead and flip that on
now i'm making some hydrogen pulling
around 20 amps
and if i go ahead and kill the power
this the cell shuts off as well that's a
nice safety feature you'll want to you
want to think about doing
in your install uh something i'd
recommend
never install a hydrogen assisted fuel
cell
uh into any vehicle uh where it's
directly wired to the battery that's
just a really really bad idea
and also always use at least a bubbler
which is this guy right there
prevents flashback basically if this
carburetor this
fuel injection system here backfires
and it's got a lead of hydrogen
coming from the line the hydrogen just
like gasoline is going to
go back into this hose more than likely
blow up the bubbler
come back to the fuel cell more than
likely blow up the fuel cell and
that won't make a very pretty picture
for this ford emblem
so uh that's my setup
hope you guys got some use out of this
this is richard with hydrogen technology
today.com
visit my website thanks guys bye